## **Software Engineer**

# **PHUOC NGUYEN**

panigo3797@gmail.com

**Q** 045 787 57782

https://panigo.netlify.com

**n** rangigo

#### **EXPERIENCE**

#### **Nord Pool**

**Software Engineer** | January 2019 - Present

[ "Maintain and develop trading platform auction based for electricity market & power exchange.", "Rewrite auction system's customer-facing application from scratch using Angular 8, TypeScript, RxJS, SCSS, Material Design and .NET Core.", "Develop multi-tenant theming API with SCSS, allow dynamic styling for user interfaces based on customers' config.", "Improve test coverage for auction system with test automation development in Node.js, Jasmine, Protractor.", "Utilize container technology (Docker, Kubernetes) to limit dependencies on existing Virtual Machines, enabling a seamless deployment pipeline", "Practice SAFe methodology as a solution to Scrum at enterprise level." ]

#### **Integrify**

Web Developer | April 2018 - December 2018

["Participate in Integrify's bootcamp and develop several side-projects in React and Node.js.", "Build Integrify's internal Student Assessment Tool from front to back with React, Redux, SCSS, Node.js and Express. Design/develop authentication flow, landing page."]

#### **EDUCATION**

Major in Software Engineering, Metropolia University of Applied Sciences.

**Bachelor of Engineering** | 2016 - Upcoming graduation 2020

Computer Science Specialized Class, VNU-HCM High School for the Gifted.

High School Diploma | 2012 - 2015

#### **SKILLS**

- JavaScript
- CSS/SCSS
- React
- Angular 2+

- TypeScript
- Node.js
- .NET
- Docker/K8s
- C#
- Azure
- JIRA
- Scrum

### **About me**

I am a full-stack software developer with hand-on experience in JavaScript related stacks and .NET development. On the frontend side I have been using HTML, CSS/SASS, React/Angular, and TypeScript. In addition, I am also familiar with Node.js, C# .NET as server-side languages, and exposed to RabbitMQ/MassTransit as communication tools between microservices. I have worked both with Agile and